manoloblahnik.com 2015-11-16

# ManoloBlahnik

Manolo Blahnik International Limited (Company Number 00971691) is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Please read this policy to understand how information about you will be treated. By visiting [http://manoloblahnik.com](http://manoloblahnik.com/) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **Act** ), the data controller is Manolo Blahnik International Limited of 250 Hendon Way, London NW4 3NL. 

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

**Information you give us.** You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our website ( **our site** ) or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to join our mailing list, or use our site, subscribe to a service we provide or enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and any other personal information. 

**Information we collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:

technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; 

information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number. 

**USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

**Information you give to us.** We will use this information:

to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;

to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;

to notify you about changes to our service;

to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 

**Information we collect about you.** We will use this information:

to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;

to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 

to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;

as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;

to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;

to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.

Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. 

Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If Manolo Blahnik International Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Manolo Blahnik International Limited, our customers, or others.

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on r secure servers. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [dataprotection@manoloblahnik.com ](mailto:dataprotection@manoloblahnik.com).

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

**CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [dataprotection@manoloblahnik.com ](mailto:dataprotection@manoloblahnik.com).

Version Date: 6 August 2015
